let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the most points scored in a game?",
    answer: "100",
    options: [
      "84",
      "92",
      "100",
      "110"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of these players were not drafted in '03?",
    answer: "Dwight Howard",
    options: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Dwayne Wade",
      "Carmelo Anthony",
      "Dwight Howard"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What team has the best NBA regular season record?",
    answer: "2015 - 2016 Golden State Warriors",
    options: [
      "2014 - 2015 Golden State Warriors",
      "1995 - 1996 Chicago Bulls",
      "2015 - 2016 Golden State Warriors",
      "2000 - 2001 Los Angeles Lakers"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who has the most NBA Championship Rings?",
    answer: "Bill Russsel",
    options: [
      "LeBron James ",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Bill Russell"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who holds the record for most turnovers in NBA History?",
    answer: "LeBron James",
    options: [
      "James Harden",
      "Karl Malone",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "LeBron James"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of these NBA Franchises never never moved cites?",
    answer: "New York Knicks",
    options: [
      "New York Knicks",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Oklahoma City Thunder",
      "Toronto Rapters"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which team has the most consecutive championship wins?",
    answer: "Boston Celtics",
    options: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of these Hawks players weren't in the 2015 All Star Game?",
    answer: "Dennis Schroder",
    options: [
      "Paul Millsap",
      "Jeff Teague",
      "Dennis Schroder",
      "Al Horford"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who was the younger player to be named NBA MVP?",
    answer: "Derrick Rose",
    options: [
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "LeBron James",
      "Derrick Rose",
      "Stephen Curry"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who is the Greatest Player of All Time?",
    answer: "Michael Jordan",
    options: [
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "LeBron James",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Shaquille O'Neal"
    ]
  },

 
];
